Audrey Taylor-Akwenye

Audrey Akwenye

2600 Lake Austin Blvd, Austin, Texas

512-658-6394 audreyakwenye@yahoo.com @audreyakwenye

Background

I am an educator who believes in everyone's ability to be successful. I have experience teaching all age groups from kindergarten to post-graduate and I have taught on three continents. I am also very passionate about Technology. I'm a creator who is excited to support and catapult other creators in the tech industry.

Experience

Lambda School / Teaching Assistant

Feb 2019 - Current, Remote

After completing my studies, I stayed on at Lambda School to assist the next Data Science cohort. I lead a support group of 7 students through the Data Science program at Lambda School. In this role, I conduct code reviews of the students in my group as well as run daily standups to review lectures and walk through any questions.

The Gardner Academy / Founder and Board Chairwoman

Aug 2011 to Feb 2018, Windhoek Namibia

With a student body of 358 students, I oversaw the academic instruction, management of human resources as well as the financials of the school. The Gardner Academy is a network of Low-Cost Private Schools in Namibia. Since moving to Austin, I have moved from director to board chairperson.

The U.S. Embassy Windhoek/ Assistant to RSO

April 2010 - Jan 2012, Windhoek Namibia

I worked in the security department ensuring that expatriates are safe in Namibia. My duties included managing the guard staff, running background checks and briefing US visitors, volunteers and state department staff on safe security.

Bezon School District / English Teacher

Aug 2006 - Nov 2006, Bezon, France

I was an English as a Second Language teacher in various middle schools in the Bezon area.

Education

Lambda University / Data Science

Data Science & Machine Learning

 $\textbf{Millsaps College /} B.A \ in \ History \ Education \ with \ minor \ in$

Education and French

August 2003 - August 2007, Jackson Ms

Skills

Data Science, Django and Flask Development, & Python

Portfolio - www.audreyakwenye.com